A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
Library of Virginia
- Series VIII: Special Projects, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
  - Correspondence and Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and Reports: Dept. of Health, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and Reports: Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and Reports: Office of the Inspector General, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Health Professions: Audit Report - Notes, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Social Services: Overview (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Dept. of Social Services Proposed Legislative Package, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Social Services: Report on Audit for the Year eneded June 30, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Disease Management - DMAS, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - DMHMRSAS Capital and Infrastructure Requirements, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - DMHMRSAS College of Direct Support Demonstration Program Final Report, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - DMHMRSAS Workforce Development Plan, 2003 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Eastern State Hospital, undated
  - Early Learning Council, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Early Learning Council / Early Childhood Summit, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Eastern State Hospital, undated (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Eastern State Hospital: Public Private Education and Infrastructure Act, 2005 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - EDS Immunization Registry and Tracking Services, undated (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Electronic Health Records: Calls, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Health Records: Task Force, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - REVIEW: Emergency Operations Briefing (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Energy Assistance Program, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Executive Agreement, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - EZ Filer, 2005 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - EZ-Filer Systems, LLC: The Solution to the Workload Gap for VA DSS, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Family and Intimate Partnet Violence Homicide, Virginia, 1999-2003 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Feasibility Study for the Two Virginia Schools for the Deaf and Blind, 2005 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - FFIS Budget Brief 05-14 President's Katrina Proposals Funded by Transfers, Rescissions, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - FFY 2006 Items on which Congressional Assistance is Sought for Virginia, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Foster Care Rates, 2002-2005 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - From Reinvestment to Transformation: Virginia's MH, MR and SA Services System, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Funding Request: Expansion of Free Clinic Disease State Management Programs, undated (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - FY 2005 State Funds for Free Clinics: Final Progress Report, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Gangs of Virginia, undated (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - General Assembly, 2005 [1] (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly, 2005 [2] (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - General Information, undated (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Get Connected!: Linking Older Adults with Medication, Alcohol, and Mental Health Resources, undated (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Gilbane, undated (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Good .. To Better ... To Great: Innovations in 10-Year Plans to End Chronic Homelessness in Your Community, undated (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - Governor's Preventing Crime in Virginia's Minority Communities Task Force Report, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - Governor's Real Estate Initiative Agency Roundtable, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Task Force on Cervical Cancer, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Task Force on Cervical Cancer, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Task Force on Information Technology in Health Care, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Task Force on Real ID Act of 2005, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - HB 1500 Final Actions, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Health and Human Resources Report, 2006 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Health and Human Resources: Update on Budget Actions Related to Offender Treatment, 2002 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Healthy Living, 2002-2005 (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Henry and William Evans Home, Winchester, 2004 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - HHR Congressional Briefing Documents, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - Human Resources Manual for Local Departments of Social Services, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Hurricane Katrina News Release, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Innovations in 10-Year Plans to End Chronic Homelessness in your Community, undated (Box 147, Folder 15)
  - Interagency Anti-Gang Work Group, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Interagency Civil Admissions Advisory Council, 2005 [1] (Box 147, Folder 16)
  - Interagency Civil Admissions Advisory Council, 2005 [2] (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Interstate Compact for the Placement of Children - First Draft, 2004 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Invitations - Secretary Woods, 2005-2006 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - It Can Happen to Anyone VHS Tape (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - ITIM Handbook: The Road to Successful IT Investment Management, 2003 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Joint Healthcare Commission, 2004 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Joint Meeting of the Community Integration Implementation Team and the Oversight Advisory Committee, 2005 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Kent Social Services - Kent County Council (UK) (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2004-2005 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2005, fo. 1 of 5 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2005, fo. 2 of 5 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2005, fo. 3 of 5 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2005, fo. 4 of 5 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Proposals, 2005, fo. 5 of 5 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Proposals: 2004 Session, 2003 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Proposals: 2005 Session (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Proposals: 2006 General Assembly Session, undated (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Session Prep. Meeting, 2004 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Session, 2005 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Studies as Required by the General Assembly, 2002-2004 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Studies as Required by the General Assembly, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 17)
  - Licensed Assisted Living Facilities and Regulations, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 18)
  - Life Journeys, Inc: Family Connections Confrencing, undated (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - Long Range Strategic and Capital Outlay Issues, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - Long Term Care and Aging Services, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Long Term Care and Aging Services, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Long-Range Strategic and Capital Outlay Issues, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 18)
  - Medicaid 1619B and Buy In, 2002 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Meetings File, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 19)
  - Memorandum re: Proposed Regulations for Assisted Living Facilities, undated (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - Memorandums, 2003-2004 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Mental Health / Mental Retardation, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Mental Health/Mental Retardation Public/Private Partnership, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Mission of Mercy: Dental Clinic and Health Fair, undated (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - National Assication of State Human Services Finance Officers - 58th Annual Conference, 225 (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - National Commission on Community Service, 2003-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - National Commission on Community Service, 2003-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - No Time to Waste: Indicators of School Readiness, 2004 Data Book (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - No Wrong Door for Long-Term Care Services in Virginia, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Nonemergency Transportation Brokerage Services, 2004 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Nottoway Work Camp - Crewe, Virginia, undated (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - Nursing Home Outreach Meeting - May 18, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Office of the Inspector General: Reports, 2005 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Oklahoma Health Care Authority: Strategic Plan and Performance Reporting State Fiscal Year, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 20)
  - Olmstead Initative, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 21)
  - Olmstead Initiative: Community Integration Implementation Team, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Olmstead Initiative: Joint Meeting of the Community Integration Implementation Team and Community Integration Oversight Advisory Committee, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Olmstead vs. Task Force, 2002 (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Overview of the Dept. of Social Services, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - Part C Program, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Part D Lawsuit, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - Personal Responsibility, Work and Family Promotion Act of 2002, 2002 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Perspectives on TANF: A Summary Report of Ten Roundtables to the Virginia Department of Social Services, 2002 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Planning District 19 Mental Health Task Force, Phase II Report, 2004 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - PPEA Proposals, 2005, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - PPEA Proposals, 2005, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 141, Folder 22)
  - PPEA Proposals, 2005, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 141, Folder 23)
  - PPEA Proposals, 2005, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 141, Folder 24)
  - Programs and Services: Office of Emergency Services, 1999 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Progress Report on Selected Information Systems Developmetn Projects in the Commonwealth, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 25)
  - Promoting Work in Public Housing: The Effectiveness of Jobs-Plus: Final Report, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - Public Private Education and Infrastructure Act - SVP, 2005 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Public Private Education and Infrastructure Act, 2005 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Publications, 2004-2005 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Publications Received, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - Quest for a Cure: The Public Hospital in Williamsburg, Virginia, 1773-1885 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Real ID Act of 2005, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 26)
  - Recommendations for Improving Assisted Living Facilities, 2004-2005 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Reference Materials, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Reference Materials, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - Region III Policy Academy, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Report of the Temporary Assistance to Needy Families Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance for the Quarter Ended December 31, 2004, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 27)
  - Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance for the Quarter Ended September 20, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 29)
  - Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance for the Quarter Ending June 30, 2005, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 28)
  - Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance, 2004-2005 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Reports and Publications, 2003-2005 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Reports, 1997-2000 (Box 145, Folder 2000)
  - Request for Proposals: Interdisciplinary Child Abuse and Neglect Advocacy Projects (draft), 2005 (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Research Material: Health Care Reform, undated (Box 141, Folder 30)
  - Restitution and Inmate Development (RAID) Program, 1997-2002 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Review of the Virginia Community Services Board Emergency Services Programs, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 31)
  - Roberts, Nancy - Speeches and Talking Points, 2003-2005 (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Rural Pace Legislation, undated (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2005 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Secure Virginia Panel: Public Hearing, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Secure Virginia Panel: Strategic Plan, 2005 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Servicemembers' Civil Relief Act, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 32)
  - Sex Offenders and Sexual Predators, 2007 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Shoveling Up: The Impact of Substance Abuse on State Budgets, 2001, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Shoveling Up: The Impact of Substance Abuse on State Budgets, 2001, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - Single Audit Report for the Year Ended June 30, 2004, 2004 (Box 141, Folder 33)
  - Slavin FOIA, 2002-2005 (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Special Report: Medical Supplies and Pharmaceuticals, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Spotlight Health, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - State Coverage Initiative, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - State Executive Council, 2003-2004 (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - State Executive Council, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - State Executive Council, 2005 Sept 20, 2005 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - State Executive Council: June 15, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - State Executive Council: November 14, 2005 Meeting, 2005 (Box 141, Folder 34)
  - State of VCU Health System Annual Briefing, 2005 Sept 15, 2005 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Statement of Need for Legislation: Dept. of Social Services, undated (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Submission to Policy Office and DPB: 2005 Legislative Proposals, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 28)
  - Substance Abuse Services Council Annual Report and Plan, 2004 (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Substance Abuse Services Council Annual Report and Plan - Draft, 2004 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Summary Report on Virginia's Drug Court Programs, 2003 (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - Supportive Education for Children of Addicted Parents: Children's Program Kit, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - TANF II: Opportunities for a Lifetime - TANF RE-Authorization Advisory Group, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - TANF Reauthorization Briefings, 2002 (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Target Industries, undated (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Terrorism and Security Awareness Orientation and Instructor Guide, undated (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - The Statistical Record of the Virginia Medicaid Program and Other Indigent Health Care Programs, State Fiscal Year 2004 (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - Thou Shalt Honor: A town hall meeting, 2002 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Tour de Food Stamps: R.A.C.E. Towards Payment Accuracy, Sept. 24-26, 2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - Tour de Food Stamps: R.A.C.E. Towards Payment Accuracy, Sept. 24-26, 2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Transformation Grant, 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Transformation Grant, 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 16)
  - Transformation Grant, 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 17)
  - Treatment Options for Offenders with mental Illness or Substance Abuse Disorders, 2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 20)
  - Treatment Options for Offenders with mental Illness or Substance Abuse Disorders, 2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 21)
  - Unfortunates Committed to Our Care: The History of Eastern State Hospital, Williamsburg, Virginia from 1865, undated (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Unsolicited Proposal: Eastern State Hospital, 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - Unsolicited Proposal: Eastern State Hospital, 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 150, Folder 16)
  - Unsolicited Proposal: Eastern State Hospital, 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 150, Folder 17)
  - Untitled (Box 140, Folder 25)
  - Use of RRASOR actuarial instrument in assessing sex offenders for civil commitment, undated (Box 141, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Beach EMS, 2005 (Box 140, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Center for Behavioral Rehabilitation, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Department of Health: Hot Button Issues, 2004 (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Department of Social Services: Workload Measures Study, undated (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Freedom of Information Act, undated (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Health Care Association: InnerView, undated (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Independence Program: Monthly Report, 2004-2005 (Box 150, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Independence Program: Monthly Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Independence Program: Monthly Report, April 2004 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Independence Program: Monthly Report, April 2005 (Box 144, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Independence Program: Monthly Report, June 2005 (Box 144, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Independence Program: Monthly Report, October 2005 (Box 141, Folder 37)
  - Virginia League of Social Service Executives: Managed Care Panel, 2003 (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, 2001-2001, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 140, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, 2001-2001, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 140, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, 2001-2001, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 140, Folder 29)
  - Virginia State Child Fatality Review Team, A Report from the, May 2005 (Box 144, Folder 33)
  - Virginia's Primary Care Association: Background Briefing Request to the Commonwealth of Virginia for Consideration of Economic Development Through Capital Funding of Community Health Centers in Medically Underserved Areas, undated (Box 141, Folder 38)
  - Virginia's Social Services System, undated (Box 141, Folder 39)
  - Weekly Reports from Agency Heads, 2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 22)
  - Weekly Reports from Agency Heads, 2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 23)
  - Weekly Reports, 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 5 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - Weekly Reports, 2004-2005, fo. 2 of 5 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Weekly Reports, 2004-2005, fo. 3 of 5 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Weekly Reports, 2004-2005, fo. 4 of 5 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Weekly Reports, 2004-2005, fo. 5 of 5 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center Six Year Capital Outlay, undated (Box 141, Folder 40)
  - Workforce Investment Act, 2003 (Box 148, Folder 24)
- Series IX: Media, 2002-2005
  - 101s A Guide to Positive Discipline (2 VHS Tapes) (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - 101s A Guide to Positive Discipline (3 CDS) (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Response to Dementia (1 VHS) (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Hyperfitness Greenbriar Elementary School, Fairfax VA (1 CD) (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Join the Voices for Recovery: Healing Lives, Families and Communities, September 2005 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Partners: The Fight for Inclusion for People with Disabilities (1 VHS) (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Talk 2 Me: A toolkit for discussing sexuality and relationships with your kids (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Virginia's EITC Initiative Coalition Building Handbook, May 2004 (1 CD) (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - 111 3.5-inch floppy disks (Box 156, Folder 1)